<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Increment when releasing a new version -->
    <integer name="news_last">401</integer>

    <string name="news_title">What\'s new?</string>
    <string name="news_messages">

        <item><![CDATA[
<b><font color="#ffffff">4.0.1</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; - Add missing currency tokens to crypto currencies filter.
<br>
&emsp; - Add BGN selection to the convert fragment when a filter was already set.
<br><br>
<b><font color="#ffffff">4.0.0</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; - We added currency filters. Go to the Currencies view and select only the currencies you are interested in.
<br>
&emsp; - We added new crypto currency sources - Cryptobank, BitcoinsHouse and xChange.bg.
<br>
&emsp; - Small but cool user interface improvements, as well as internal optimizations and improvements.
<br><br>
<b><font color="#ffffff">3.2.1</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; - We fixed an issue with the currencies not being downloaded by the app\'s background service.
<br>
&emsp; - We removed the refresh button on the Wallet screen. Entries are reloading automatically.
<br>
&emsp; - Minor optimizations.
<br><br>
<b><font color="#ffffff">3.2.0</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; - Added Forex House, Changepartner and Allianz Bank currency exchange sources.
<br>
&emsp; - Added rates for Georgian Lari, Moldovan leu, New Taiwan Dollar, Qatari Riyal, Saudi Riyal, Vietnamese Dong, Jordanian Dinar.
<br>
&emsp; - Added rates and conversions sharing feature.
<br>
&emsp; - Added calculator when entering Wallet asset values.
<br>
&emsp; - Lots of performance improvements.
<br><br>
<b><font color="#ffffff">3.1.0</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; - Added Bitcoin currency info using Bitcoin Solutions as source.
<br>
&emsp; - Added multiple currency selection on Convert screen.
<br>
&emsp; - Added currency exchange info screen.
<br><br>
<b><font color="#ffffff">3.0.0</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; - Fixed a problem with currency updates via the background app service.
<br>
&emsp; - Added <b>Wallet</b> function. You may now get a calculation of profits and losses for all currencies in your possession.
<br>
&emsp; - Added SG Expressbank and UniCredit Bulbank currency exchange sources.
<br>
&emsp; - Added <b>Wi-Fi</b> only background service downloads option. Requires the <b>ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE</b> permission.
<br>
&emsp; - Added green coloring of the best currency convert rate for each added source.
<br>
&emsp; - Added short vibration when removing convert or wallet entries. Requires the <b>VIBRATE</b> permission.
<br><br>
<b><font color="#ffffff">2.1.0</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; - Added a list of all downloaded currency rates in the past 3 days. Tap on a currency from a given source to view the data.
<br>
&emsp; - Added a menu <b>Clear</b> function to convert screen.
<br>
&emsp; - Added missing currency country flags.
<br>
&emsp; - Fixed an issue with fetching latest currency rates after weekends.
<br><br>
<b><font color="#ffffff">2.0.0</font></b>
<br><br>
&emsp; -  Now displays currency rates from several currency exchange sources.
<br>
&emsp; - BNB is now excluded, as it does not provide direct exchange services.
<br>
&emsp; - Added a calculator when entering currency values to convert.
<br>
&emsp; - Fixed task bar issue on Android 4.4 devices.
        ]]></item>

    </string>

</resources>